When are you gonna
break up with him?
What do you mean?
It's already been
over half a year
It's about time to end it
It's no help
having a relationship
with someone like him
If it's a contract
there will be a period
It depends on me
Is that what they said
in the agency?
It ends when you end it?
I told you it's no good…
Why do you care?
What?
It's none of
your business
whatever happens
to him and me
Why not?
I'm not a child
You don't need to worry
about such things
You think…
I'm doing this
only because
I'm worried about you?
If it's not…
why are you doing this?
Because I like you
more than a friend
Just go back to sleep
Soobin, I…
Don't
I'm not asking
for your answer
I like you too